mulpix.com 2018-03-19

# Privacy policy

Privacy Policy

  1. Thank you for visiting Mulpix.com (the "Site") and reviewing the Privacy Policy Mulpix ("Mulpix", "We", "Us", "Our" ). By using or accessing the Site, you expressly consent to Our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Information collection and use

Collection of information

  1. You are free to browse the Site without revealing any personal information making it possible to identify you. However, once you have sent us your identifiable personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. 
  2. We collect one type of information from Users of the Site: Automatic Anonymous Information (AAI) 
  3. The Site make it possible to monitor certain information automatically, based on your behaviour. This information does not identify you personally. We use this information to improve the Content and functionality of the Site, and to better understand and satisfy our visitors. This information may include the browser you use, your IP address or other information. This information is referred to herein as the AAI. 

Shared information

  1. We may be required by law enforcement, government administrators, and/or judicial authorities to provide personally identifiable information. We will disclose personally identifiable information upon receipt of a court order, or if required to co-operate with law enforcement, administrative or other governmental agencies. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that We in good faith believe to be unlawful. 
  2. Our service providers who help with Our business operations and employees on a need-to-know basis. Third parties to whom you explicitly ask Us to send your information or you consent to and are notified when using a specific service. Business entities, if We plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity, should such a change in control occur. 

Links

  1. On the Site you will find various links directing you to Third Party Sites or to Third Party Content. Mulpix shall not be liable for the links posted by Users or the privacy policies of such third parties. The Terms of Use Mulpix Site, and in particular this Privacy Policy, do not govern to Third Party Sites or to Third Party Content which the User accesses from the Site. 

Use of cookies

  1. We use cookies to collect non personal information, help smooth user experience, remember you on future visits, better understand how users engage with the Site so we can enhance the User experience. 
  2. The use of these cookies is optional; you can configure your browser not to accept, or to only sometimes accept, cookies. 
  3. However, for optimum use of the Site, we advise you to accept Mulpix cookies. Certain functions may require the use of cookies in order to function correctly. 

Security

  1. Mulpix uses its best efforts to ensure the confidentiality of your personal data. 
  2. Mulpix uses secure technology according to industry standards to protect the Content and the User privacy. All Mulpix personnel have a duty to respect the confidentiality of the Users. A confidentiality obligation is included in each employment contract of Mulpix employees with access to personal data. 

Modification of the privacy policy

  1. Mulpix reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Any modification or amendment will be effective upon Mulpix posting the same on the Site. Continued use by you of the Site after Mulpix has posted an updated version of the Privacy Policy implies your consent to the Privacy Policy as modified or amended. Consequently, it is important that you regularly read this Privacy Policy to ensure that you are fully aware of any changes that may be made to them. 

Contact

  1. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us.
